i-freelancer.org 2011-08-13

# Privacy Policy | Freelance Jobs

##  Privacy Policy 

**Privacy Statement**

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This Site contains links to other sites. These include links to partners that we believe may be of interest to you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Browsing the Site**

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

**Personal Information**

We do not post our users’ personal information for any reason. When posting their portfolios and information, our users decide for themselves how much contact information they wish to display.

All users should be aware that when they display or distribute personal information (such as their email) or a link to a personal homepage, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which we are not responsible.
